Guide to the Stein and Day Publisher Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Production Files
  - The Run to Morning by Jack Higgins, 1981 (Box 46)
  - Sacred Honor by Raymond B. Lech, 1984 (Box 47)
  - The Second Stone by Leslie A. Fiedler, 1969 (Box 47)
  - Secrets by F. Lee Bailey, 1979, (3 folders ) (Box 47)
  - Seige by Edwin Corley, 1969, (2 folders ) (Box 47)
  - Sex in History by Reay Tannahill, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Shaw's Etcetera by Alan Chappelow, 1968 (Box 48)
  - Slings and Arrows by Robert Lewis, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Solo by Jack Higgins, 1980, (2 folders ) (Box 48)
  - The Solution to All the World's Problems by David Frost, 1968 (Box 48)
  - Somebody Pays by Ray Russell, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Southern Ladies and Gentlemen by Florence King, 1974 (Box 48)
  - Sovereign State by Anthony Sampson, 1972, (2 folders ) (Box 49)
  - Sparrow in the Snow by Sylva Darel, 1973 (Box 49)
  - The Specialist by Gayle Rivers, 1985, (2 folders ) (Box 49)
  - Spider Scott novels by Kenneth Royce. (Box 49)
  - Spinfishing by Norman Strung, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Sports and American Society by Charles Cohen & Robert Marcus, 1974 (Box 49)
  - The Squeeze by David Craig, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Stalin by Leon Trotsky, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Stalin Account by Kenneth Royce, 1985 (Box 50)
  - The Stay-Married Handbook by Lawrence Weinberg, 1978 (Box 50)
  - Stein and Day. Clippings. (Box 50)
  - Stein and Day. Correspondence with Penguin Books, 1964-1970 (Box 50)
  - Stein and Day. Documents. (Box 50)
  - Stein and Day. General file., (2 folders ) (Box 50)
  - Stein and Day. Legal material: Antitrust case. (Box 50)
  - The Stein and Day Baseball Date Book by Rich Marazzi, 1981 (Box 50)
  - The Stein and Day Dictionary of Definitive Quotations by Michael McKenna, 1983 (Box 51)
  - Stein & Day vs McCall Corp. Legal material. (Box 51)
  - Storm in the West by Sinclair Lewis & Dore Schary, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Straight Talk to Parents by Mary Susan Miller & Samm Sinclair Baker, 1976 (Box 51)
  - Strange Communists I Have Known by Bertram D. Wolfe, 1982 (Box 51)
  - Streets of Gold by Evan Hunter, 1985 (Box 51)
  - Super Joe by Joe Charboneau, Burt Graeff, and Terry Pluto, 1981 (Box 51)
  - The Supercops by L. H. Whittemore, 1973 (Box 51)
  - Superstars, Stars, and Just Plain Heroes by Nathan Salant, 1980 (Box 52)
  - The Swimmer by Eleanor Perry, 1967 (Box 52)
  - The Talking Ape by Keith Laidler, 1981 (Box 52)
  - Talking to Yourself by Pamela E. Butler, 1981 (Box 52)
  - Tannahill, Reay. General File (Box 52)
  - The Tears of Chalbi by Kenneth Royce, 1976 (Box 52)
  - That Pellet Woman! by Betty Pellet with Alexander Klein, 1965 (Box 52)
  - Theme and Variations by Yehudi Menuhin, 1971 (Box 52)
  - Theomatics by Jerry Lucas and Del Washburn, 1979 (Box 53)
  - Think by William Rodgers, 1970 (Box 53)
  - The Third Bullet by Arnold Stream, 1985 (Box 53)
  - The Thirties by Alan Jenkins, 1976 (Box 53)
  - The Thoroughly Tasteful Dirty Jokebook by Shelli Sonstein, 1984 (Box 53)
  - The Tibbets Story by Paul W. Tibbets, 1978 (Box 53)
  - Tiger by Nigel Slater, 1985 (Box 53)
  - Tillich, Hannah 3 unpublished short stories (Box 54)
  - Time No Longer by Andrija Ruharich, 1981 (Box 54)
  - To Catch a King by Harry Patterson, 1979 (Box 54)
  - To Stand at the Pole by William R. Hunt, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Tony the Iceman by Chris Kazan, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Total Self-Knowledge by Ernest Dichter, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Touch Me by Suzanne Somers, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Touch the Devil by Jack Higgins, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Trace Your Roots by Grahame Hughes, 1977 (Box 55)
  - The Truth about Medical Malpractice by Ronald E. Gots. (Box 55)
  - Two Men Who Saved France by Major-General Sir Edward Spear, 1966 (Box 55)
  - The Ultra Americans by Thomas Parrish, 1987 (Box 56)
  - The Understudy by Elia Kazan, 1975, (2 folders ) (Box 56)
  - Up From LIberalism by William F Buckley, Jr., 1984 (Box 56)
  - The Valhalla Exchange by Harry Patterson, 1976 (Box 56)
  - The Value of Nothing by John Weitz, 1970 (Box 56)
  - Vietnam by Hugh Lunn, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Vigilante by William Tucker, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Voices by Seymour Shubin, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Wadleigh, John. General File. (Box 57)
  - Waiting for the End by Leslie A. Fiedler, 1969 (Box 57)
  - The Warburgs: The Story by David Farrer, 1974 (Box 57)
  - WASP, Where is Thy Sting by Florence King, 1977 (Box 57)
  - The Week France Fell by Noel Barber, 1974 (Box 57)
  - Weiner's Herbal by Dr. Michael Weiner, 1979, (1 folder ) (Box 58)
  - What To Do When the Russians Come by Robert Conquest and Jon M. White, 1984 (Box 59)
  - What You Can Do About Baldness by Edmund Van Deusen, 1977 (Box 59)
  - When the Kissing had to Stop by Constantine FitzGibbon, 1977 (Box 59)
  - Whiting, Charles. General File. (Box 59)
  - Why Are They Lying to Our Children? by Herbert London, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Witches' Sabbath by Maurice Sachs, 1971 (Box 59)
  - 'Wiv a Little Bit o'Luck' by Stanley Holloway, 1967 (Box 59)
  - Wolfe, Bertram and Ella. General File. (Box 59)
  - Your Child's Right to Sex by Hal M. Wells, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 59)
- Series III: Manuscripts
  - The Angel of Zin by Clifford Irving, 1983 (Box 59)
  - Answer to History by Mohammed Reza Pahlavi (Shah of Iran), 1980 (Box 60)
  - Answer to History by Mohammed Reza Pahlavi (Shah of Iran), 1980 (Box 61)
  - Confessional by Jack Higgins, 1984 (Box 62)
  - The Final Conclave by Malachi Martin, 1978 (Box 62)
  - Hoffa: The Real Story by James R. Hoffa, 1975 (Box 63)
  - How To Protect Yourself Against Cops in California and Other (Box 63)
  - Strange Places by F. Lee Bailey, 1982 (Box 63)
  - The Messengers Will Come No More by Leslie Fiedler, 1974 (Box 63)
  - My Story by Marilyn Monroe (Box 63)
  - The Nine Lives of Mickey Rooney by Arthur Marx, 1985 (Box 64)
  - A Partisan View by William Phillips, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Secrets by F. Lee Bailey, 1979 (Box 65)
  - The Tibbets Story by Paul W. Tibbets, 1978 (Box 65)
  - To Catch a King by Harry Patterson, 1979 (Box 66)
  - The Understudy by Elia Kazan, 1975 (Box 66)
  - The War Against the Terrorists by Gayle Rivers, 1986 (Box 66)
  - The War Against the Terrorists by Gayle Rivers, 1986 (Box 67)
  - What To Do When the Russians Come by Robert Conquest and Jon M. White, 1984 (Box 67)
  - With a Cast of Thousnads by Jill Schary Zimmer (Box 67)
  - Wynner by Mel Torme, 1977 (Box 68)
- Series IV: Photographs
  - Backus, Jim and George Burns, (1 photograph ) (Box 69)
  - Brown, Christy, (4 photographs ) (Box 69)
  - Brown, Claude, (4 photographs ) (Box 69)
  - Chesterton, Gilbert Keith, (1 photograph of a painting ) (Box 69)
  - Fiedler, Leslie A., (1 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Fisher, Bobby, (3 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Frost, David, (6 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Hart, Benjamin, (53 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Himes, Chester, (5 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Howar, Barbara, (1 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Olivier, Laurence, (38 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Oppenheimer, Robert, (1 photogrpah ) (Box 69)
  - Patterson, Harry, (12 photogrpah ) (Box 69)